maggylondon.com 2012-10-03

# Security and Privacy - Maggy London

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Maggy London International, Ltd. ("Maggy London") respects your privacy. Accordingly, it has adopted the following privacy policy. This policy notifies you of: 

  * what personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through Maggy London's website;
  * the organization collecting the information;
  * how the information is used;
  * with whom the information may be shared;
  * what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  * the kind of procedures we employ in an effort to hinder the unauthorized access, deletion, alteration, use or disclosure of information you provide to Maggy London;and
  * how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information you provide to us.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us by sending an email to [customerservice@maggylondon.com](mailto:customerservice@maggylondon.com "Email us") or by calling 1-888-430-9672. 

## **SCOPE OF POLICY**

This policy applies to Maggy London's treatment of personally identifiable information that Maggy London collects through Maggy London's website and when you use Maggy London's services. The policy does not apply to practices of companies whose websites may be linked to Maggy London's. For access to the privacy policies of such linked websites, please refer to the information provided by such websites at their home pages. Also see the paragraph below under the heading "Hypertext Links".

## **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Maggy London collects personally identifiable information when you request information from Maggy London. On such occasions, Maggy London may ask for your name, email address, zip code and personal information concerning your interests, occupation, gender and other demographic information. Maggy London also receives and records information from server logs from your browser including cookie information relating to pages requested.

Maggy London does not seek to collect such information from persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any such information to us. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 18 who has provided such information to us, please inform us (through the Maggy London website or telephone number listed above) and we will remove such information from our database as described further below. 

In addition, no person (of any age) is required to provide us with the personally identifiable information we request. If you do not wish to provide such information, you are free not to do so. Your provision of requested information to us through Maggy London's website or other means is presumed by us to be voluntary and with your consent to the uses described herein. If after submitting personally identifiable information to us, you wish to "opt-out," please contact us as noted above and we will remove your information from our database as set forth below in the section titled "Managing Your Information." Please know that such a decision will not stop advertising or content that is generated prior to the time when we can accomplish the removal of your information.

Maggy London uses the information you provide to us to customize advertising and content that we present to you, to contact you concerning specials and new products and to enhance our product offerings. Maggy London will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party except when:

  * You have been given an opportunity to "opt out" of sharing the information and have declined to exercise that right within the time period provided;
  * Maggy London must share the information in order to provide a product or service that you have requested, in which case we will demand that any third party we use to fulfill your order agree that it does not have the right to use the personally identifiable information other than to fulfill your request; or
  * Maggy London is required to respond to subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure.

## **USE OF COOKIES**

Maggy London uses cookies to enhance the interactive nature of your Internet experience and to provide a convenient feature to save you time. Cookies enable Maggy London to quickly retrieve specific information from previous visits and to recall features that you may have customized on your browser.

## **MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION**

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all your personal data collected by us via Maggy London's website, as well as to require us to delete your data if you no longer want us to process it. You can make such a request or a related inquiry by sending an email to customerservice@maggylondon.com or by calling 1-(888)-430-9672. Please note that there may be a small charge for making an access request or it may be free, depending on the circumstances. You can find out more details by emailing or calling us as provided above. We will keep your data as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this privacy policy. You may choose not to receive unsolicited marketing material from Maggy London and you have the right to request deletion of your Maggy London account information, subject to Maggy London's need to keep appropriate archives of its business operations.

## **SECURITY**

Maggy London employs reasonable measures to maintain all personally identifiable information provided by you on computer servers in a controlled and secured environment in an effort to hinder unauthorized access, loss, alteration, use or disclosure of such information. Maggy London utilizes secure socket layer encryption technology and firewall network protection to protect personally identifiable information that is transmitted to Maggy London's e-commerce websites. Unfortunately, the nature of the Internet is such that information may be transmitted over networks without appropriate security measures and may be accessed, deleted, altered, used or disclosed by unauthorized persons.

Because of the international nature of the services and products provided by Maggy London's website and the nature of Maggy London's business, personal data may, subject to applicable law, be transferred internationally throughout Maggy London world-wide for the purposes described above. This may mean that personal data are transferred to countries which do not have laws or regulations which protect personal data, such as the United States, where the server for Maggy London's website is located. We use reasonable measures to limit the disclosure of the data you provide to us only to certain staff within Maggy London and its affiliates (i.e. staff whose job it is to process your inquiries and survey answers or otherwise to administer Maggy London's website, and those staff involved in the provision of Maggy London services and products which may be of interest to you) and to require that they process the data only for the purposes identified in this privacy policy.

To protect Maggy London's customers from fraudulent transactions on Maggy London's e-commerce websites, all orders are subject to review and verification. As part of the verification process, an order may be temporarily placed on hold in order to verify credit card billing information, which may include contacting the credit card holder.

## **MODIFICATIONS TO THIS POLICY**

Maggy London may make modifications or amendments to this policy from time to time. In the event that such changes alter how Maggy London gathers, processes, uses or discloses your personally identifiable information, Maggy London will post such changes on our website.

## **INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY**

Maggy London, its suppliers, licensors, or the original creators of all materials on Maggy London's website own all copyrightable subject matter on Maggy London's website and all trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes or other proprietary rights of Maggy London and/or such other parties. No license to or right in any such copyrights, trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes and other proprietary rights of Maggy London and/or other parties is granted to or conferred upon you.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Maggy London hereby authorizes you only to copy the content herein solely for your personal and private use in learning about, evaluating, or acquiring Maggy London products. Except where expressly noted, no other permission is granted to print, copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, upload, download, store, display in public, alter, or modify the content contained on this website. Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this website may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. Any other use of materials on this website, including reproduction for purposes other than those expressly permitted herein, modification, distribution, or republication, without prior written permission of Maggy London is strictly prohibited. Any copy made by you as permitted herein must retain all copyright and trademark notices, including any other proprietary notices, contained in the materials. The use of such materials on any other website or in any environment of networked computers is prohibited.

## **HYPERTEXT LINKS**

In the event this website contains hypertext links to websites that are not created or maintained by Maggy London, this privacy policy applies only to Maggy London's website and not to any of these third party websites. Maggy London is not responsible for the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of those third party websites. The inclusion of any link to such websites does not imply endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by Maggy London of the third party websites. Maggy London disclaims any liability for links (1) from another website to this website, and (2) to another website from this website. Maggy London cannot guarantee the standards of any website to which links are provided on Maggy London's website, nor shall Maggy London be held responsible for the contents of those websites, or any subsequent links. For this reason, Maggy London does not represent or warrant that the contents of any third party website is accurate, compliant with state or federal law, or compliant with copyright or other intellectual property laws. Maggy London does not endorse the contents of these third party websites in any way. Also, Maggy London is not responsible for web casting or any other form of transmission received from any linked website. Any reliance on the contents of a third party website is done at your own risk, and you assume all responsibilities and consequences resulting from such reliance.

## **CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES**

When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to this website, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information gathered from you for entry will be used and disclosed.

## **ONLINE SURVEYS**

We may from time to time conduct on-line surveys. When you complete an online survey, we may ask for certain information including your age, zip code, shopping habits, email and/or mailing address. This information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## **PCI Overview**

The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) is a security standard which at Tier 1 Certification and compliance ensures unbeatable security and protection of sensitive customer information including credit cards.  
The requirements for Tier 1 Certification include: 

  * Security management policies;
  * Security policies;
  * Security procedures;
  * Network architecture;
  * Software Design;
  * Critical Protective Measures.

Websites go through a rigorous INDEPENDENT audit and significant investment to attain Tier 1 PCI DSS certification. The purpose is to ensure that their customers' data is as safe as possible when they purchase products online.  
Venda is the only global website provider to provide enterprise wide PCI DSS Tier 1 Certification. Visit [www.venda.com](http://www.venda.com/) for more information.
